nodecraft.com 2017-02-24

# Privacy Policy - NodeCraft Hosting LLC

_This policy was last modified on May 10th, 2014._

### I. OVERVIEW #

NodeCraft Hosting LLC values its visitors’ privacy. This privacy policy summarizes what information we might collect from a registered user or other visitor ("you"), and what we will and will not do with it. Hereinafter, NodeCraft.com may be referred to as "NodeCraft", "we", "us", or other first-person pronouns. Please note that this privacy policy does not govern the collection and use of information by companies that we do not control, nor by individuals not employed or managed by us. If you visit a Web site that we mention or link to, be sure to review its privacy policy before providing the site with information. 

We reserve the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner.

### II. YOUR INFORMATION #

It is your decision whether to disclose personally identifiable information to us, although if you elect not to do so, we reserve the right not to register you as a user or provide you with any service. "Personally identifiable information" dictates information that can be used to identify you as an individual, including, but not limited to: 

  * your name, company, email address, phone number, billing address, and shipping address
  * your NodeCraft user ID and password
  * any account-preference information you provide us
  * session data for your login session
  * external identifiers used in conjunction with your NodeCraft account (such as your social media handles)

If you do provide personally identifiable information to us, either directly or through a reseller or other business partner, we will: 

  * not sell or rent it to a third party without your permission — although unless you opt out, we may use your contact information to provide you with information we believe you need to know or may find useful, such as, but not limited to, news about our services and products and modifications to the Terms of Service
  * take commercially reasonable precautions to protect the information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction
  * not use or disclose the information except:
    * as necessary to provide services or products you have ordered, such as, but not limited to, providing it to a carrier to deliver products you have ordered or communicating with your bank or payment provider to collect payment
    * in other ways described in this privacy policy or to which you have otherwise consented
    * in the aggregate with other information in such a way so that your identity can not reasonably be determined (for example, but not limited to, statistical compilations)
    * as required by law, for example, but not limited to, in response to a subpoena or search warrant
    * as necessary to enforce the Terms of Service
    * in the event of another party acquiring our business
    * as necessary to protect the rights, safety, or property of NodeCraft, it's users, or others, which may include, but not be limited to exchanging information with other organizations for fraud protection and/or risk reduction

### II. OTHER INFORMATION #

We may collect other information that cannot be readily used to identify you, such as, but not limited to the domain name and IP address of your computer. We may use this information, individually or in the aggregate, for technical administration of our Web site(s); research and development; customer and account administration; and to help us focus our marketing efforts more precisely. 

### III. COOKIES #

NodeCraft uses "cookies" to store personal data on your computer. A "cookie" is an alphanumeric identifier that is unique to your browser. The cookie will identify your browser to us when you visit our web site so that we may customize your visit. We may also link information stored on your computer in cookies with personal data about specific individuals stored on our servers. If you configure your Web browser to prohibit the storage of cookies, you may not be able to use some or all of the features of our Web site(s). 

### IV. EXTERNAL DATA STORAGE #

We may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted. This includes, but is not limited to your credit card information, which is stored via a third party service identified as Stripe. Their privacy policy concerning this information can be referenced [here](https://stripe.com/us/privacy) as well as their [security](https://stripe.com/help/security) precautions. 

### V. YOUR PRIVACY RESPONSIBILITIES #

To help protect your privacy, you agree to: 

  * never share your user ID or password with anyone else
  * log off the NodeCraft site when you are finished
  * take customary precautions to guard against "malware" (viruses, Trojan horses, bots, etc.), for example by installing and updating suitable anti-virus software

### VI. EUROPEAN UNION USERS NOTICE #

NodeCraft's operations are located primarily in the United States. Should you provide information to us, the information will be transferred out of the European Union (EU) to the United States. By providing personal information to us, you are consenting to its storage and use as described herein. 

### VII. INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM CHILDREN #

Our service is not available to children under the age of 13, and we will not intentionally maintain information about anyone under said age. Any persons requesting service that are under the age of 13 must have a parent or guardian do so in place of themself. (See the U.S. Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act).
